(blood sloshing)
(blood sizzles)
Oh, that blood,
don't touch that.
You think, I don't know that?
(blood whooshes)
(Kugisaki gasps)
Now run away with
your backs to me.
(ground rumbling)
-(Itadori grunting)
-(streams of blood crashing)
Come on Kugisaki, is that
the fastest you can run?
Oh, shut up!
(streams of blood sloshing)
-(Kugisaki grunts)
-(Kugisaki thuds)
-(Itadori grunts)
-(stream of blood crashing)
I've got your back.
Oh, great.
(ground thuds)
Huh?
(ground thundering)
(Kugisaki groans)
What amazing speed,
and while carrying someone too.
(streams of blood gushing)
They're getting away.
Well, no matter.
(Itadori grunts)
(Itadori whooshes)
(Itadori and Kugisaki thud)
(Itadori and Kugisaki grunt)
Okay, we're out of his range.
[Kugisaki] Well done.
I'll make sure you get a medal.
[Itadori] Yeah, yeah.
[Kugisaki] I'm
kidding, thank you.
(Itadori gasps)
(Itadori grunts)
-(blood gushing)
-(Kechizu gurgling)
(blood swooshing)
I guess it took a shortcut
and got here ahead of us.
-Itadori!
-(blood smashes)
(Kugisaki groans)
[Itadori] Kugisaki!
You don't need to worry
about that too much.
My younger brother's blood
doesn't have the
same quality as mine
and even mine probably
won't kill you outright,
unless you manage to get
your entire body bathed in it.
Though, I can assure
you it will hurt like hell.
Now we've reached the time
where our technique
actually begins.
Rot Technique! Decay!
(flesh squelching)
[Kugisaki] Huh?
-(Opening theme music)
-(singing in Japanese)
My blood, like
that of my brothers
is absorbed by the victims,
through their wounds
and membranes.
And then once any of us
brothers activate the technique
it quickly begins
to rot you away
from the point of incursion.
I'd give that young
man about 15 minutes.
10 minutes, max,
for you, young lady.
By morning, nothing
but bones will remain.
If it's a technique,
we just need to
make them release it.
So, then it is toxic.
The end result is
essentially that of a poison,
but, I assure you our technique
is purely one of decomposition.
Now that I finished
revealing our technique
they'll actually end
up dying even faster.
So, what will you do now?
Elder brother, these sorcerers
didn't amount to much.
[Narrator] During the Meiji era,
there was a girl
with a unique trait
that allowed her to bear
a cursed spirit's child.
She conceived a child
without knowing how
and the criticism she endured
from her parents and
relatives was extreme.
She fled with her baby's corpse,
ending up at a temple run
by a certain jujutsu sorcerer.
That's where her luck ran out.
(blood splats)
Noritoshi Kamo.
In jujutsu sorcery's legacy,
he's remembered as
the most vile of sorcerers.
A disgrace to the
three major clans.
He was captivated
by the possibility
of a child born of a
human and a cursed spirit.
Nine times he impregnated her.
Nine times he aborted her.
All records of how he did it
and what happened to her
afterward, were destroyed.
The Cursed Wombs Death
Paintings, one through three,
became cursed objects
powerful enough
to be classified
as special-grade.
Perhaps the origin of that power
was the mother's
resentment, or perhaps...
[Eso] I have no
memories of a mother.
Humans, sorcerers.
It's not that I hold any
special grudge against them.
For 150 years, we've
remained sealed away
with nothing but each
other's existence to rely on.
We'll side with
the cursed spirits.
Are you sure about that?
They seemed shady
to me, elder brother.
The future those
cursed spirits painted
is more convenient for us.
That's all there is to it.
You can forget about owing them
for our current manifestation.
And now listen up brothers.
Eso, you live for Kechizu.
Kechizu, you live for me.
And I'll live for you, Eso.
We three are one.
I live for my brothers.
If it is what my brothers desire
I will gladly give my life
to grant that wish for them.
If the suffering is too great
would you like me to end
you right away as a merciful act?
(Kugisaki laughs)
A technique that
guarantees victory once it hits.
You two are strong.
You're screwed though,
'cause that makes me the
worst possible match for you.
(blue flame whooshes)
Straw Doll Technique!
-(nail clangs)
-Resonance!
(Eso gags)
(blood patters)
Let's play a game of chicken.
You don't like pain
very much, do you?
Then you'd better start crying
and release your technique!
(Kechizu moans)
[Eso] A technique that turns
the curse back on the user.
It is a game of chicken.
So unless I release
our technique,
this pain will continue?
[Kugisaki] Straw Doll
Technique, Resonance.
It's a technique
that deals damage
to the target's main body
by driving cursed energy
through an effigy and a
lost portion of the target.
The technique's range is
broad and the effect varies
with the difference in strength
between us and the
value of the lost portion.
As far as Straw Doll
Technique is concerned,
blood isn't very valuable.
But, Resonance uses it
as the link to its target
and the blood from both
of them that's inside me now
is strongly linking us and
they're Rot Technique together.
It's a nice surprise
that it worked on the
younger brother, too.
If I'm going to die here anyway
then I'll just keep on
hammering Resonance into them.
Yes, that pain is quite intense,
but no matter how
many times she does it,
it won't end our lives.
So, as long as we hold
out, you'll be the ones to die.
Not to mention,
while Decay is active
the pain and poison will
keep you from moving.
(energy thunders)
(Kechizu growls)
[Eso] How were you
able to move that well?
(Eso grunts)
(Kechizu growls)
(nail clangs)
[Kugisaki] Resonance!
(punch thuds)
Itadori is the vessel
for Ryomen Sukuna,
the King of Curses
and Deadly Poisons.
So, he has resistance
to all forms of poison.
[Eso] The end result is
essentially that of a poison
but I assure you, our technique
is purely one of decomposition.
[Kugisaki] He's
probably feeling pain
from the decomposition
but the resulting
poison doesn't affect him
and if it's just pain...
(Itadori grunts)
(Itadori thuds)
Yuji Itadori!
(Itadori grunting)
Will never stop!
-(Itadori grunting)
-(Kechizu groans)
Kechizu!
(nails clang)
Just shut your mouth, huh?
Resonance!
It's nothing!
(energy thundering)
He switched.
The woman was close to death
so he matched her against
my brother who's also dying.
Does she think she can
stop my movement forever?
Damn you!
Do I released the
technique or not?
I can't go and save
my brother like this.
I can't unleash Wing
King while Decay is active.
But, does that woman
have enough strength left
to kill my brother?
Even with all of
her interference,
this man won't be able
to kill me before she dies.
So, I cannot release
the technique!
(Kechizu gasping)
(Kechizu yells)
(Eso sobs)
[Choso] We three are one.
[Eso] I live for my brothers.
(rock music)
-(Itadori and Eso grunting)
-(energy thundering)
I was already releasing
it before I even knew it.
(punches thudding)
Wing King!
-(streams of blood swooshing)
-(rock music)
(Kechizu growling)
(nail clangs)
(Itadori thuds)
(blue light swooshes)
(Kechizu roars)
-(blue light swooshes)
-(rock music)
(Kugisaki and Itadori grunt)
♪ It's not right or wrong ♪
-(blood gushes)
-(Kechizu roars)
What? What was that
black light I saw just now?
I know I reinforced my
arm with cursed energy
just before taking his punch,
and the next thing I knew,
my whole arm and shoulder
had been blown away.
(gasps) Younger brother,
please, don't you die.
Elder brother!
(Itadori grunts)
All right, I haven't shown
you this one yet, have I?
(fingers snap)
(nail sizzles)
Hairpin.
(Kechizu thuds)
Don't worry.
I'll soon send your
older brother to join ya.
Kechizu.
[Choso] We three are one.
[Eso] I'm sorry, elder brother.
(Itadori gasps)
Even though I was
with him, I... (gasps)
Why isn't this thing vanishing?
Is it still alive?
(gasps) No!
It's not a cursed spirit,
it has a physical body!
-(horn blares)
-(Kugisaki gasps)
Watch your ass!
Christ.
(passenger yelps)
(driver gasps) Sawamura?
Speed up.
Hit the brakes and you're dead.
Both you and him, you got that?
(tires squealing)
-(passenger whimpering)
-(blood squelches)
(passenger screams)
Listen, you, don't follow me.
Once I'm healed,
I'll make sure to kill these
two, especially that woman.
I'm sorry, Kechizu.
I wasn't able to mourn you
but I promise you, I
will get revenge for...
What the hell?
What is she doing?
Kugisaki!
(Straw Doll swishes)
(nail clangs) (blue
light swooshes)
Yeah, don't rush me, okay?
Straw Doll Technique!
Resonance!
-(blue light swooshes)
-(weapon clangs)
(blood sloshes)
(Eso gasps)
[Narrator] Once sorcerers
land a Black Flash,
they temporarily enter a state
that athletes
commonly call the zone.
(Itadori thuds)
That hurts. (yells)
So it wasn't a technique
to turn the curse of the user.
(blue light sizzles)
Sorry.
(blue light swooshes)
(Itadori thuds)
(energy thundering)
(somber music)
(smoke hisses)
That hurt.
(game clicking)
All right, Geto, pay up.
What's the matter, Choso?
Come on.
(object cracks)
Whoa, hey, what'd
you do that for?
Both of my bothers just died.
You can sense that from here?
[Choso] What's going on?
It'd be one thing if he
was fully manifested,
but I can't believe both
my brothers were killed
by a single finger
of a cursed spirit.
Just a minute.
[Mahito] Crap, there
aren't any spares.
Why did you have
to break that one?
[Geto] I just got the report.
Eso and Kechizu were killed
by first-years
from Jujutsu High.
Yuji Itadori and his group.
(Mahito laughs)
(blinkers clicking)
[Voice Mail] The person you
have dialed is not responding.
If you feel you have
reached this number in error-
-Why don't they answer?
-(car revving)
Where did those brats go?
[Itadori] Kugisaki, you okay?
Oh, I'm okay.
I might have some
scarring, though.
I wonder if those two old dudes
in the truck are all right?
And the poisons...
Wow, I wonder if we head
home now if Shoko will be awake
and if she'll still be sober?
It's creeping me out
that you're being so quiet.
[Itadori] I was wondering,
was this your first time
killing instead of exorcizing?
Mm-hmm. What about you?
Yeah, I did have to
do it one other time.
No, I guess it's
wrong to call it one.
There were three.
Then I think you're doing
worse here than I am
from the sound of it.
What just happened
meant nothing to me.
Just another day for a sorcerer.
And, I'm no Fushiguro here,
but ultimately there are only
so many people we can save.
Like, if I think of my life
as a bus ride, you know,
I don't want to get my
heart swayed by someone
who shouldn't have had
a seat in the first place.
Too mean?
But, then sometimes
there are people like you
who bring their own seat
and just sit right down.
If it helps, we didn't have
room back there to worry about
whether they were cursed
spirits or curse users.
Even if they were human,
we don't have a technique
to keep anyone that
strong restrained long-term.
You know that, right?
Yeah, but, he was crying
watching his brother die.
[Kugisaki] I see.
[Itadori] Don't get me wrong.
I'm happy you and I were
spared and we're still alive.
It's a big relief.
But, the fact remains
tears were shed
over the lives I ended tonight.
That's all.
[Kugisaki] I see.
In that case, you
and I are accomplices.
[Both] (gasp) Fushiguro?
(moans) Oh, you're back.
Glad you're safe.
[Both] Yay, I was scared!
I thought you were
dead for sure, thank god!
Could you lower
your voices please?
My head hurts.
Don't go to sleep
holding Sukuna's finger.
That thing's dangerous.
And how would you
know about the finger?
[Kugisaki] You have the
energy to ask about that?
Nope, let's go ahead
and contact Nitta.
We need to seal this
from cursed spirits.
They're coming for it.
Oh wait, should I eat it?
[Kugisaki] It's not
some midnight snack!
We don't have a clear idea
of how many fingers
you can handle.
So, don't eat it.
But I will hand it over to you
since you have the most energy.
I'll say it once more
though, do not eat this.
(mouth gulps)
Huh?
(grunts) He thinks I have
the intelligence of a dog!
-I said don't eat it!
-He said don't eat it!
Huh? What?
I'm not the one
who ate it, he is!
Sukuna didn't even
warn me this time either.
[Gojo] The Sukuna within you
will try to regain his power
and that will lead
us to the fingers.
Has Gojo just been
winging it this whole time?
[Fushiguro] You
just realized that?
There you are, you
three little jerks!
What have you been
doing all this time?
[Itadori] Oh, it's Nitta.
[Kugisaki] And it
sounds like she's lost it.
[Nitta] I called! What's
the big idea, huh?
-All right, let's go.
-(Nitta yelling)
[Nitta] Keep things from
going sideways and you three-
-[Kugisaki] I'm hungry.
-(Nitta yelling)
I wonder if there's a
Splendid Sushi around here.
[Itadori] Splendid
Sushi's bullet train
was awesome, wasn't it?
[Kugisaki] Shut up.
Turns out it wasn't
just a cursed
spirit with a finger.
When we analyzed the
corpses, what a surprise.
It was the manifestation
of the other goods
and each of them took
out one special-grade.
And this year's first-years
are the cream of the crop.
I guess it's my amazing
skill as an instructor.
[Utahime] I don't want
any long chats with you
on my day off.
You're calling
about arrangements
for the drinking party, right?
[Gojo] Well, find
any candidates?
No, none.
Everyone's busy,
including myself.
What now? Should I
try inviting the students?
Sure, I'm a lightweight,
so I don't mind
if the party's alcohol-free.
You can do it.
Keep asking around.
(Gojo sighs)
You never know what
might be listening
around Utahime, after all.
I don't want to think about
one of the students
being the traitor.
This is such a pain.
Well, leave the
rest of you, Mei Mei.
(mellow music)
(Mei Mei laughing)
[Fushiguro] Don't
talk about them
resonating with Itadori.
[Kugisaki] Are you
certain about that?
I think so.
The case is over, though.
The only ones likely to
notice would be us and Nitta.
Itadori and Sukuna's
manifestation
was only the trigger.
The curse of Yasohachi
Bridge could've started
killing at any moment.
Besides, when he
swallowed that first finger
it was to save me.
But, there's no way he'd
be satisfied with just that.
So, don't tell him.
I won't say anything.
Girls know how to be discreet.
This is all your fault.
You took me in.
And now the severed parts
of my soul have all awakened.
(laughs) In order to save
lots of people, was it?
You little punk.
Other people are gonna
die because you live.
[Itadori] Hey, don't
say that to Fushiguro.
How are you going to feel
when someone you save
goes on to kill
someone else later?
[Itadori] Don't you dare say it.
(Zen'in grunting)
(Panda grunts)
(Maki gasps)
(punch thuds)
(Panda laughs)
[Toge] Mustard leaf.
Your reactions don't
seem very sharp today.
What's the deal?
Shut up.
All that time off
cost me my edge.
Yeah, obviously.
So, did you hear
about the first-years?
Yeah, I heard they took
out three special-grades.
Is that true?
[Toge] Salmon.
Well, in that case, we
don't want to fall behind.
So, let's get to it.
[Toge] Roe.
Yeah! (gasps)
(Maki grunts)
[Panda] Hey, you hit
me for real that time!
[Maki] It wouldn't
be good training
if I wasn't serious, would it?
[Toge] Kelp.
Even among sorcerers,
the rank of special-grade
is a position beyond
the normal scope.
It's my conviction,
that it's the first-grades
who should lead the other
sorcerers of the jujutsu world,
given all the confidential
information and the danger.
That, along with the pay
that they have to accept
is nothing like what those
semi-first-grade and
below must deal with.
So, with that in mind, what
are your recommendations?
Maki Zen'in, Panda.
Megumi Fushiguro
and Nobara Kugisaki
and then, my
brother Yuji Itadori.
So by my name, Aoi Todou...
[Mei Mei] And
by mine, Mei Mei...
[Aoi Todou and Mei Mei] We
hereby recommend these five
for promotion to first-grade.
(Itadori moaning)
[Itadori] I just think you're
buying way too much stuff.
[Kugisaki] Half of
that is yours, isn't it?
Huh? No.
Only one is mine.
-(Itadori grunts)
-(paper bag rustling)
(Itadori sighs)
Huh?
You drop even one of
those bags and I'll kill you.
Oh, right.
(punch thuds)
(Itadori grunts)
I just told you that if you
drop even one you're dead!
I'm sorry, it was an accident!
-(Kugisaki growls)
-You just have too many bags!
If any of my stuff gets damaged,
-you're going to pay for it!
-(phone buzzing)
Fushiguro.
-(Itadori and
Kugisaki yelling) -Yes.
Yeah.
All right, see ya.
What?
Gojo says to
come in, it's urgent.
[Itadori] Huh?
[Kugisaki] Yeah? What for?
An assignment.
He said it was top secret.
[Kugisaki] Huh?
But we just finished
doing a big mission for him.
Sounds good to me.
If Gojo's telling us it's
top secret, it must be big.
He says that a lot.
Only every time.
Yeah, but so what?
Let's go.
(rock music)